<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LOB.DATA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LOB.DATA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean White Theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/readme/</guid>
      <description>Clean White Theme for Hugo CleanWhite is a clean, elegant, but fully functional blog theme for Hugo. Here is a live demo site using this theme.
It is based on huxblog Jekyll Theme and Clean Blog Jekyll Theme.
These two upstream projects have done awesome jobs to create a blog theme, what I&amp;rsquo;m doing here is porting it to Hugo, of which I like the simplicity and the much faster compiling speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean White Theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/readme2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/readme2/</guid>
      <description>Clean White Theme for Hugo CleanWhite is a clean, elegant, but fully functional blog theme for Hugo. Here is a live demo site using this theme. It is based on huxblog Jekyll Theme and Clean Blog Jekyll Theme. These two upstream projects have done awesome jobs to create a blog theme, what I&amp;rsquo;m doing here is porting it to Hugo, of which I like the simplicity and the much faster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/about/</guid>
      <description>Meu nome é Luciano Oliveira Batista, Engenheiro Químico formado pela Universidade Estadual de Santa Cruz (UESC) e Cientista de Dados em formação. Ao longo da minha formação como Engenheiro pude trabalhar com diversas ferramentas analíticas aplicadas em projetos de pesquisa, como matlab, R e Statistica.
Há aproximadamente 1 ano me apaixonei pela área de Data Science, e decidi estudar e agregar à minha formação acadêmica este tópico extremamente útil e aplicável.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>