<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>R - Tag - LobData</title>
        <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/tags/r/</link>
        <description>R - Tag - LobData</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.lobdata.com.br/tags/r/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Effective approach to analyze correlation coefficients</title>
    <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/correlation_analysis_in_r/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Luciano</author>
    <guid>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/correlation_analysis_in_r/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/img/autocorrelation.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><p></p>
<p><strong>Correlation analysis</strong> is a key task when you&rsquo;re exploring any dataset. The principal objective is to find linear relationships between features that can help to understanding the big picture.</p>
<p>Probably, the best way to see correlations between variables is to use scatterplots, but in most of time you&rsquo;re working with a high dimensional dataset with a high number of variables, in these situations you have two major problems:</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Hypothesis Testing by Computational Methodology - Part 1</title>
    <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/hype_test/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Luciano</author>
    <guid>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/hype_test/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/img/testing.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><h1 id="introduction">Introduction</h1>
<p>This is the first of two articles that we&rsquo;ll talk about two different approaches to perform hypotheses tests, covering the <em>classical</em> and <em>computational</em> methodologies. In the end I&rsquo;ll show you one R package (<code>Infer</code>) capable to execute any of these methods in an easy, flexible, and less error-prone way.</p>
<p>In the second article, we&rsquo;ll go deeper in a hands-on experiment using the Infer package, if you already know the package and want to see more code than text, click <strong>here</strong>.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Perform Correlation Analysis in Time Series data using R?</title>
    <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/r_correlation/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Luciano</author>
    <guid>https://www.lobdata.com.br/posts/r_correlation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/img/cor_ts.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><h1 id="what-is-it-correlation-analysis">What is it correlation analysis?</h1>
<p>The concept of correlation is the same used in non-time series data: <em>identify and quantify the relationship between two variables.</em> Due to the continuous and chronologically ordered nature of time series data, there is a likelihood that there will be some degree of correlation between the series observations.</p>
<p>Measuring and analyzing the correlation between two variables, in the context of time series analysis, can be understood by two different aspects:</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
