<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Time Series on LOB.DATA</title>
    <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/tags/time-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Time Series on LOB.DATA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.lobdata.com.br/tags/time-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demand Forecasting of Brazilian Commodities</title>
      <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/2020/10/25/demand-forecasting-of-brazilian-commodities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lobdata.com.br/2020/10/25/demand-forecasting-of-brazilian-commodities/</guid>
      <description>Demand Forecasting of Brazilian Commodities Soybean, Corn, Sugar, Soybean Meal, Soybean Oil and Wheat (left to right).
Demand Forecasting is a technique for estimation of probable demand for a product or services. It is based on the analysis of past demand for that product or service in the present market condition. Demand forecasting should be done on a scientific basis and facts and events related to forecasting should be considered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Perform Correlation Analysis in Time Series data using R?</title>
      <link>https://www.lobdata.com.br/2020/09/15/how-to-perform-correlation-analysis-in-time-series-data-using-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lobdata.com.br/2020/09/15/how-to-perform-correlation-analysis-in-time-series-data-using-r/</guid>
      <description>What is it correlation analysis? The concept of correlation is the same used in non-time series data: identify and quantify the relationship between two variables. Due to the continuous and chronologically ordered nature of time series data, there is a likelihood that there will be some degree of correlation between the series observations.
Measuring and analyzing the correlation between two variables, in the context of time series analysis, can be understood by two different aspects:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
